I will not abandon her.
We only know she was taken.
Not who took her.
I can help with that.
Ursa has an enemy among the also a war war named Derval.
Expect to find him lurking somewhere near the border.
I've already sent an agent to investigate.
He'll be waiting for word from us in the market place and I can't move troops to the border without provoking the awesome.
But I could send a few Van Guardsman
and perhaps an exceptionally gifted Nora as well.
More
enough,
more, more.
Oh,
me.
What?
What
low and quiet does.
Hello.
Three years.
Can't get a wink of sleep beds around, just like people, too.
Damn song.
This must be pitch clothes.
Murad Agent should be in the market.
Got a pair of sturdy OSCE around hands out of
work.
There's work here, but
what?
No sign of Murat Guy.
He's had plenty of time to investigate.
We'd better look for him.
Damn right.
Well, someone left here recently and they were in a hurry.
Wayne, sleep my bed from a car just like them.
Every resident of this city deserves safety and security.
That's the deal
has to be Murat's guy.
Durables.
Thugs must have made.
Maybe because you found something.
Look at this.
I think he drew back with his own right.
Those kind of maps, you know, You better follow.
That might be pitch, Cliff.
He marked a spot to the north.
Could be Devil's location.
My men are waiting outside.
Attack.
Grab him and meet you there.
Let's make this quick.
No.
Here they come.
Oh,
tomorrow Now.
True
machines.
Looks like they've been chained up.
Revolves it, tinker.
Probably experiments.
Strips them for parts.
Used them to make some trouble.
I'll go in first.
Hold off until the fighting starts.
All right?
We've got your back
two.
Yeah.
Girls may
got to get over.
I hope so.
Yeah.
I told you.
No.
Well, yeah.
Can't close the gap.
Frightening.
No.
Their boss says you gotta eat.
Okay.
No more
must be in there.
We have to get through.
They must use these to protect themselves from that offer.
Sound
person.
Aaron,
They have all tried to break me.
Shows what he knows.
I should have been with you.
Why didn't you come from me?
I know I'm a useless trunk, but no idiot.
I got a message from Derval saying he wanted to parlay.
I didn't come for you because I know it was a trap.
I couldn't let you get hurt.
I just didn't think of that good a trap.
I thought I could take him out.
Now listen.
Evolves planning something big in Meridian.
He said he'd force of odd to watch as the smoke darkens their precious son.
Your king needs you.
No more playing around.
You're gonna have to grow up fast.
I will.
I promise you.
Damn well better little brother
person.
No, no, please.
I won't let you down.
I promise.
Every time.
I'm so sorry.
You've gotta find dirt
but meridians.
A big place.
I'll look through his things.
Maybe we can narrow it down.
Just give me some time with her son.
No,
Such a strange device.
It's beautifully crafted.
What happens when I turn it on?
I think I've got it working
there.
No.
Let's say something.
Both of you doves.
I don't know.
What do you want me to say?
Whatever you want.
I just want to hear your voice and keep it for later.
I'll sing Papa
Shit
there a song and a laugh.
Even betterthan words.
Now I can hear them whenever I want.
We're done them off to bed with you.
Good night, Mama.
Good night, Papa.
Is she gone?
What are we going to do?
The raids are getting closer and closer to Main Spring.
How much longer can we hide?
Like this keepsake from his family?
Devil's got nothing left to lose.
This machine's been picked apart with precision.
What's Derval learned from always tinkering?
I don't even want to know.
See
Devil's records?
Maybe.
I just know it's about crafting
on a letter tucked between the pages.
Lots of blaze headed to Meridian.
If we find it, I'll bet we find her vault too.
I think I found something that can help.
Let's head back to the palace.
Go.
I won't be long, but I need to tend to my sister.
They saw us.
You
again.
Talks must be here for this
only experience.
Adventure.
One
grafting
on a letter tucked between the pages.
Lots of places headed to Meridian.
My loyal customer ale.
Unfortunate.
I hope your plans for a forge in Upper Meridian are moving forward and we're honoured.
You chose is to provide the blaze.
You need We've received payment for the third shipment, and we're most thankful for your prompt remuneration.
Unfortunately, are hunters are struggling to cover the order.
We apologise for the delay, but this is an unusually large request.
As soon as we have it, we'll deliver it to your warehouse.
Has promised without most respect Guaranteed Master Mainspring Machine Makings plan Charter 17 21.